[
{"question": "IDCMOA", "response": "COMIDA" },
{"question": "CEHLEUP", "response": "PELUCHE" },
{"question": "PATLPO", "response": "LAPTOP" }, 
{"question": "ÁIPDOR", "response": "RÁPIDO" },
{"question": "PÁZLI", "response": "LÁPIZ" },
{"question": "LDEUC", "response": "DULCE" },
{"question": "CSÚMIA", "response": "MÚSICA" },
{"question": "EMÍITL", "response": "LÍMITE" },
{"question": "MRÁACA", "response": "CÁMARA" },
{"question": "TORTARE", "response": "RETRATO" },
{"question": "CÉHILE", "response": "HÉLICE" },
{"question": "NELÚT", "response": "TÚNEL" },
{"question": "ARBÑA", "response": "BAÑAR" },
{"question": "ANJRMA", "response": "MANJAR" },
{"question": "STICHE", "response": "CHISTE" },
{"question": "USEOQB", "response": "BOSQUE" },
{"question": "IRTGAR", "response": "GRITAR" },
{"question": "ELUOCL", "response": "CUELLO" },
{"question": "ÍNDARJ", "response": "JARDÍN" },
{"question": "ECAMTA", "response": "MACETA" },
{"question": "UGPLAR", "response": "PULGAR" },
{"question": "RECRAR", "response": "CERRAR" },
{"question": "HULCRA", "response": "LUCHAR" },
{"question": "NABCLO", "response": "BLANCO" },
{"question": "ARLBILR", "response": "BRILLAR" },
{"question": "ILBORL", "response": "BRILLO" },
{"question": "ECZAIN", "response": "CENIZA" },
{"question": "MOSRBA", "response": "SOMBRA" },
{"question": "RSEETU", "response": "SUERTE" },
{"question": "NICBOA", "response": "BOCINA" },
{"question": "AFRAIJ", "response": "JIRAFA" },
{"question": "CCOEH", "response": "COCHE" },
{"question": "SMAUPE", "response": "ESPUMA" },
{"question": "AMRATP", "response": "TRAMPA" },
{"question": "TLAFUA", "response": "FLAUTA" },
{"question": "ARECDU", "response": "CUERDA" },
{"question": "AVODEN", "response": "VENADO" },
{"question": "REPOR", "response": "PERRO" },
{"question": "DLARLIA", "response": "ARDILLA" },
{"question": "CDRUAO", "response": "CUADRO" },
{"question": "PRUECO", "response": "CUERPO" },
{"question": "OLEBATL", "response": "BOTELLA" },
{"question": "PAMLRAA", "response": "LAMPARA" },
{"question": "FERPUEM", "response": "PERFUME" },
{"question": "SCODI", "response": "DISCO" },
{"question": "TANPIUR", "response": "PINTURA" },
{"question": "RUITGARA", "response": "GUITARRA" },
{"question": "TANMA", "response": "MANTA" },
{"question": "AMRARIO", "response": "ARMARIO" },
{"question": "CLIOABEBIT", "response": "BIBLIOTECA" },
{"question": "RRILIABE", "response": "LIBRERIA" },
{"question": "CSELEUA", "response": "ESCUELA" },
{"question": "IVERUSDDAIN", "response": "UNIVERSIDAD" },
{"question": "TARUEP", "response": "PUERTA" },
{"question": "JOEESP", "response": "ESPEJO" },
{"question": "ENAATNV", "response": "VENTANA" },
{"question": "TIBBSCOMULE", "response": "COMBUSTIBLE" },
{"question": "LATAPN", "response": "PLANTA" },
{"question": "DOCAMER", "response": "MERCADO" },
{"question": "CARMADOR", "response": "MARCADOR" },
{"question": "PLTARNAE", "response": "PARLANTE" },
{"question": "LARCLUE", "response": "CELULAR" },
{"question": "PUTDAOCOMRA", "response": "COMPUTADORA" },
{"question": "TERNEF", "response": "FERNET" },
{"question": "ULCICHLO", "response": "CUCHILLO" }
]
